A Guide to Records of the Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commission, 2000-2009 (bulk 2000-2005)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commission, 2000-2009 (bulk 2000-2005)
The Library of Virginia
44460
3 cu. ft. (3 boxes)
Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commission.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and confidential information is restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78, 2.2-3800, and 2.2-3705.1-8. Types of previous restricted information may include, but are not limited to: privacy protected information and attorney-client privileged material.
Acquisition Information
Transferred on Sep. 9, 2009.
Biographical Information
On 10 July 2000, Governor James Gilmore issued Executive Order Number 66 creating the Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commission (VRTAC). The Commission was formed to advise the governor on appropriate research and technology strategy for the Commonwealth. The Commission advised the governor on procedures and guidelines for awarding grants from the Commonwealth Technology Research Fund. The Commission also advised the Executive Branch on critical issues relating to the role of science, technology, research and development, and technology commercialization in promoting the global competitiveness of the Commonwealth. The Commission consisted of thirty-three members appointed by the governor, including the Secretaries of Commerce and Trade, Education, and Technology. The Center for Innovative Technology was responsible for the majority of the funding of the Commission. On 1 July 2009, the Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Council merged with the Innovative Technology Authority (ITA) forming the Innovation and Entrepreneurship Investment Authority (IEIA).
Scope and Content
The collection contains records from the Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commission, including general files, minutes, meeting notes, reports, and agendas, among other items.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in its original order.
Contents List
- VRTAC General, 2005-2008 (Box 1)
- VRTAC General Chronological, 2004 (Box 1)
- VRTAC General Chronological, 2003 Oct.-Dec. (Box 1)
- VRTAC General Chronological, 2003 July-Sept. (Box 1)
- VRTAC General Chronological, 2003 May-June (Box 1)
- VRTAC General Chronological, 2002 (Box 1)
- VRTAC Meeting, 2005 Mar. (Box 1)
- VRTAC Meeting, 2005 May (Box 1)
- VRTAC Meeting, 2005 Sept. (Box 1)
- VRTAC Meeting, 2005 Nov. 15 (Box 1)
- Virginia's Defense and Homeland Security Industry, 2005 (Box 1)
- VRTAC-Creation of New High Technology Industries in Virginia, 2003-2005 (Box 1)
- H.B. 545 Study, 2004 (Box 1)
- VRTAC IP Studies, 2000-2002 (Box 1)
- VRTAC-Incubator Sub. Report, 2004-2005 (Box 1)
- VRTAC-R&D Strategies for the Commonwealth-HB 2760, 2003 (Box 1)
- Capitol Hill Day, 2003-2005 (Box 1)
- VRTAC-Capitol Hill Day, 2000 (Box 1)
- VRTAC Members, 2005 (Box 1)
- VRTAC Meeting, 2004 Nov. 16 (Box 1)
- VRTAC Meeting, 2004 Sep. 21 (Box 1)
- VRTAC Attendance, n.d. (Box 1)
- VRTAC, 2004 May 18 (Box 1)
- VRTAC Meeting Agendas, 2003-2004 (Box 2)
- VRTAC-Detailed Agenda, 2001 May 27 (Box 2)
- VRTAC Meeting, 2004 May 18 (Box 2)
- VRTAC Meeting, 2004 Sep. 21 (Box 2)
- VRTA Meeting, 2004 Feb. 24 (Box 2)
- Folder Handout Example, 2004 (Box 2)
- VRTAC Minutes, 2000-2004 (Box 2)
- VRTAC-Public Meeting Notice, 2004 (Box 2)
- VRTAC-Operations Plan, 2003-2004 (Box 2)
- VRTAC Meeting, 2003 Nov. 20 (Box 2)
- VRTAC Meeting, 2003 Sep. 30 (Box 2)
- VRTAC, 2000 (Box 2)
- VRTAC-Report of Gov's Adv. Board for VBI, 2003 (Box 2)
- (Box 2)
- VRTAC-Report: Research and Development Srategies for the Commonwealth of Virginia, 2003 (Box 2)
- VRTAC-Report: The Creation of New High-Technology Industries in Va, 2003 (Box 2)
- VRTAC-Advocacy Subcommittee, 2003-2005 (Box 2)
- Research and Technology Agenda 2000 for Virginia's Industries and Universities, 2000 Mar. 29 (Box 2)
- VRTAC Intellectual Property Subcommittee, 2000-2002 (Box 2)
- VRTAC Minutes and Attachments, 2002 Aug.-Dec. (Box 2)
- Minutes and Attachments, 2002 Jan.-June (Box 2)
- VRTAC Minutes and Attachments, 2000 Apr.-2001 Dec. (Box 2)
- VRTAC Meeting, 2001 Oct. 22 (Box 2)
- VRTAC Annual Reports to Gov. Board Profiles, 2005-2009 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Quarterly Meeting, 2009 May 19 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Quarterly Meeting, 2009 Mar.17 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Quarterly Meeting, 2008 Nov. 13 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Quarterly Meeting, 2008 Sep. 16 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Quarterly Meeting, 2008 May 20 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Quarterly Meeting, 2008 Mar. 18 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Meetings-Subcommittees, 2007 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Quarterly Meeting, 2007 Nov. 13 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Quarterly Meeting, 2007 Sep. (Box 3)
- VRTAC Quarterly Meeting, 2007 June (Box 3)
- VRTAC, 2007 June 13 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Quarterly Meeting, 2007 Mar. 20 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Quarterly Meeting, 2006 Nov. 14 (Box 3)
- Minutes, 2006 Sep. (Box 3)
- VRTAC Quarterly Meeting, 2006 Sep. 19 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Univ/Fed Lab Subcommittee Meeting, 2006 July 17 (Box 3)
- Minutes, 2006 May (Box 3)
- Minutes, 2006 Mar. (Box 3)
- VRTAC Quarterly Meeting, 2006 Mar. 21 (Box 3)
- Education Subcommittee Minutes, 2006 May 16 (Box 3)
- Univ-Federal Lab Subcommittee, 2007 (Box 3)
- Minutes, 2006 May 16 (Box 3)
- Minutes, 2006 July 17 (Box 3)
- Minutes, 2006 Sep. 19 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Reporting Templates, 2006 (Box 3)
- NanoBiotech News-Misc., 2005-2006 (Box 3)
- Nanomedicine, Device and Diagnostics Report, 2005 (Box 3)
- Nanomedcine, 2006 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Outgoing Correspondence, 2003-2006 (Box 3)
- (Box 3)
- VRTAC Transition Notes, 2004 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Bylaws, 2004 (Box 3)
- DLAS Procedures (Legislative Report), 2002-2004 (Box 3)
- Governor's Working Papers-VRTAC Board File, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
- VRTAC-Legislation, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Committee Assignment, 2003-2006 (Box 3)
- VRTAC Commission Members, 2004-2009 (Box 3)